Jewish War Veterans Collection 0009.001.003a
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Photographs:Individuals
  - Individuals/Kohn, Harold, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Koppelman, Marcus, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Kramer, David, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Lebetkin, George, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Lebetkin, Harold, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Levy, Uriah P., c. 1817, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Mann, Norman and Sheldon, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Marlow, George, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Mayer, Nathan, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Mazur, Mortimer, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Meltzer, Irving, see: Zionism, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Postman, Benjamin, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Rechtschafer, Herbert Charles Oversize drawer, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Richman, Milton, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Rosenberg, Morris, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Rosenburg, Milton, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Rosner, Saul, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Rudman, Jack, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Ruffkess, David, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Saltzman, Seymour/in Calcutta with other Hartford area military personnel, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Schwartz, Joseph, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Shapiro, Paul, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Sherrow, Monroe, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Silver, Lawrence J., undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Simon, Louis B., undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Simon, Saul, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Simon, Saul, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Sherrow, Monroe, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Tabatsky, Israel, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Theodore, Jules, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Wax, Julius, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Weinstein, Isadore, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Weinstein, Isadore, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Weisman, Morris, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Wolinsky, Isadore, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Wollman, Solomon, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Wright, Oscar, undated (Box 2)
  - Individuals/Yaffo, William, undated (Box 2)